i'm dedicating this olympia win to my
late father don heath who passed away in
march you know obviously at that time i
had just recently lost my father
and my focus was honoring him
taking it up another notch
using that energy but i told my father
before he passed that you know i'm gonna
bring one home for him and that's what i
intend to do i'd be foolish to come up
here like i said before that's what the
first three should have been
that's what the first three should have
been i respect your father i respect
anyone that has had a father i didn't
have one you know what not enough is
enough enough is enough this whole
fourth is enough before nothing enough
is another 13 is the past you know what
pat you've talked about the past your
whole entire career making excuses i
specifically told my ex-wife he's going
to start a fight he said how do you know
this i said cause that's what i would do
come on kai give me three
here we go fact one we'll outweigh him
by 40 pounds fact two will be wider fact
three
it's all over from the rear and that's
just that's how it's gonna be
i was like okay
and then he asked me to say the question
and i let him know phil give me three
facts as to why kai can't beat you on
stage
2011 2012 and 2013.
everybody's hyped up i gotta calm this
down because i gotta save this for
tomorrow i'm explaining this to my
family and friends i said just
understand come tomorrow it's gonna get
ugly